{
    "subject": "resource/Norris_v._Ireland",
    "predicate": "property/judge",
    "object": "C. Russo",
    "human_readable": "The judge in Norris v. Ireland was C. Russo.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9472874999046326,
            "question": "C. Russo played what role in the Norris v. Ireland case?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9337757229804993,
            "question": "Who was the judge in the Norris v. Ireland case?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8886014223098755,
            "question": "Give the name of the judge involved in the Norris v. Ireland case."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.849168062210083,
            "question": "What was the name of the judge who ruled on the Norris v. Ireland case?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8318977355957031,
            "question": "What is the full name of the judge in the Norris v. Ireland case?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8181898593902588,
            "question": "Can you identify the judge involved in the legal case Norris v. Ireland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.811369001865387,
            "question": "What was the name of the judge presiding over the Norris v. Ireland case?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7881596088409424,
            "question": "In which legal case did C. Russo serve as the judge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.657192051410675,
            "question": "Who presided over the Norris v. Ireland court proceedings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4941866099834442,
            "question": "C. Russo is known for their role in which legal case?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The judge in Norris v. Ireland was C. Russo.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1754_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who presided over the Norris v. Ireland court proceedings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1754_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which legal case did C. Russo serve as the judge?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1754_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of the judge presiding over the Norris v. Ireland case?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1754_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1754_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1754_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1754_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1754_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1754_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1754_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1754_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1754_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1754_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1754_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\nThe judge in Norris v. Ireland was actually O'Higgins (Chief Justice), not C. Russo.\n\nSo, the answer is:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nThe information provided does not mention a judge named C. Russo in the context of the case Norris v. Attorney General (Ireland). Instead, it mentions Chief Justice Tom O\u2019Higgins and other judges involved in various court cases related to homosexuality in Ireland."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Chief Justice O'Higgins was the judge in Norris v. Ireland, not C. Russo.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text discusses the Norris v. Attorney General case and specifically names Chief Justice O\u2019Higgins as the judge who delivered the leading judgment upholding the legal provisions criminalizing homosexuality.  It also mentions Mr. Justice Henchy and Mr. Justice Niall McCarthy as dissenting judges.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information does not mention a judge by the name of C. Russo in relation to Norris v. Ireland, nor are they mentioned as being involved in any other way with the case or the individuals involved in it (Tom O'Higgins, David Norris, Mr Justice Henchy, etc.).",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information mentions Chief Justice O\u2019Higgins as the judge who delivered the leading judgment in Norris v. Ireland, not C. Russo.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}